pennystockegghead.com 2018-07-16

# Privacy - The Penny Stock Egghead | Proven Penny Stock Trading System!

## Privacy Policy

 **The following must be read in its entirety before purchasing and/or using any information contained on PennyStockEgghead.com.**

#### Privacy Policy:

PennyStockEgghead.com ("Egghead" or "Site") has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how Egghead collects information from all end users of its Internet services (the "Services")-those who access some of its Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or pay a service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members")-what Egghead does with the information they collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such info. Egghead request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

#### Service Providers:

Egghead uses ClickBank.com ("ClickBank") to provide payment processing on its Site. When you purchase Egghead products and services, it will share your name, address, and credit card information as necessary for ClickBank to provide that service. Egghead and ClickBank are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

#### Links to Other Sites:

Egghead expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including its partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through its Site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit the Egghead Site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, via the Egghead Site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Egghead is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without Egghead's knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Egghead and this policy.

#### Responses to Email Inquiries:

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries Egghead, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry it receives. Egghead does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. Egghead may or may not retain these emails for its records and only for use as a reference.

#### Testimonials:

If you submit a testimonial, you should be aware that any Personally Identifiable Information you submit, such as your name, website, city and/or country of residence may be displayed on the Egghead Site, where it could potentially be used by third parties to contact you, or send you unsolicited messages. Egghead is not responsible for the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to submit in a testimonial.

#### Legal:

Egghead reserves the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when it believes that disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on its website; or to protect Egghead and its officers, agents, servants, members, affiliates, directors, contractors or employees.

#### IP Addresses:

Egghead may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with its Site or web server, and for the general administration of its website. Your IP address, should you decide to register and/or create a PennyStockEgghead.com account, is also used to help prevent you from creating duplicate accounts.

#### Cookies:

Upon your first visit to this Site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell Egghead who you are. Egghead has two primary uses for its cookies. First, it sometimes use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate its website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested. Secondly, Egghead may use cookies as part of its authentication system when you login to your account. If you select the "remember me" option when logging in for instance, the Egghead Site will set a cookie so that you do not have to login again the next time you visit PennyStockEgghead.com. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this Site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

#### Newsletters:

If you wish to subscribe to the PennyStockEgghead.com newsletter(s), Egghead will use your email address to send the newsletter to you.

#### Choice/Opt-Out:

Egghead will provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving its newsletter, in which case your email address is permanently removed from its database. If you no longer wish to receive the Egghead newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

#### Children's Privacy:

Protecting children's privacy is especially important to Egghead. It is Egghead's policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore, you must be eighteen (18) years or older to access this website. If you are under eighteen years of age, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Due to the age restrictions for use of this website, no information obtained by this website falls within the Child Online Privacy Act (COPA) and is not monitored as doing so.

#### Questions Regarding the Egghead Privacy Policy:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact Egghead through the contact information provided on this website.

#### Revisions to This Disclaimer:

PennyStockEgghead.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify our Privacy Policy, our Disclaimer, and its other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner by updating its postings. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these terms, conditions, and notices, and any additional terms posted on PennyStockEgghead.com. Your continued use of the PennyStockEgghead.com website and/or email newsletter after the effective date of such changes constitutes your acceptance of and agreement to such changes.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on July 1st, 2014.
